themepalace.com 2019-07-12

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last modified and published on May 23, 2018 and will take effect on May 25, 2018.

Theme Palace, LLC. (“Theme Palace,” “we,” or “us”) knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. Theme Palace is a marketplace for WordPress themes and plugins. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by Theme Palace when you use the Theme Palace Market Service, how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. This Privacy Policy applies to our Service, which includes www.themepalace.com, also referred to as “Site”. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Service.

#### What Information Do We Collect?

We collect information from you when you register, place an order, issue support ticket and subscribe to our newsletter. In this process you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, website URL, mailing address and phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

#### What Do We Use Your Information For?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To administer and expand our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers.
  * To process transaction
  * To send periodic emails
  * To notify you about important changes to this website, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

You may notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking the unsubscribe link contained in each such email.

#### What Are Cookies?

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

#### Do We Use Cookies?

Yes we use cookies to understand and save your preference for future visits.

#### Do We Disclose Any Information To Outside Parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose Personal Information to any third party unless required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to:

  * conform to the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities;
  * to enforce our Terms of Service, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, or to protect the security or integrity of our Site; and
  * to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Theme Palace, our Users or others.

#### What About Other Websites Linked to This Site?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our site. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our site to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including sites which have a link on our site, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

#### Payment Services

We offer Stripe and PayPal integration. All Stripe and PayPal transactions are subject to the respective policies, Stripe Privacy Policy available at https://stripe.com/ie/privacy and PayPal Privacy Policy available at https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full. We do not control Stripe or PayPal’s use of the data it collects.

* Support Service 

We offer support service by the dedicated team in company named “WEN Solutons Pvt. Ltd”. So, when you use these service. You agree to their privacy policy at http://wensolutions.com/privacy-policy

#### Data Transfers outside the EEA

If you are resident in the European Union, please note that as we are located in the United States and sub-office in Nepal, when you provide us with your Personal Information we will process it in countries outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”), such as the United States and Nepal, which may not provide the same level of data protection as in your jurisdiction. This is necessary in order to perform our services. Regardless of where your Personal Information is located, we will adopt measures to protect your Personal Information as set out below.

#### How Do We Protect Your Information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. All supplied sensitive/credit information transmitted are encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

#### Compromise of Personal Information

In the event that Personal Information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will promptly notify those persons whose Personal Information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

“Do Not Track” Signals. Your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a “do not track” signal to websites and online services you visit. At this time there is no consensus among industry participants as to the meaning of “do not track” in this context. Like many other websites, the Sites are not configured to respond to “do not track” signals from browsers. [Click here](https://allaboutdnt.com/) to learn more about “do not track” signals.

#### Your Choices About Your Information

##### All Users

  * _Decline to Submit Information_ : You may, of course, decline to submit Personal Information through the Service, in which case Theme Palace may not be able to provide certain services to you. 
  *   * _Update Account Information_ : You may update or correct your account information and email preferences at any time by logging in to [your account](http://themepalace.com/my-account/) settings page. You can also exercise any of your rights by contacting us directly at [info[at]themepalace[dot]com](mailto:info@themepalace.com).
  * _Unsubscribe from emails_ : To unsubscribe from a particular newsletter, click the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of that email newsletter. When we send newsletters to subscribers we may allow advertisers or partners to include messages in those newsletters, or we may send dedicated newsletters and marketing messages on behalf of those advertisers or partners. We may disclose your opt-out choices to third parties so that they can honor your preferences in accordance with applicable laws.
  * _Blocking cookies_ : Certain browsers may be configured to notify you when you receive cookies, or allow you to restrict or disable certain cookies. If you choose to disable cookies, however, that could affect certain features of the Service that use cookies to enhance their functionality. Please see here for Information About Our Use of Cookies And Similar Technologies.

##### EEA Residents

If you are located in the EEA, or if otherwise required by applicable law, you also have the following rights in relation to your information:

  * Inspection and access: you can request from us a summary and a copy of any Personal Information we hold about you
  * Correction/addition/removal: where you believe your information is inaccurate or incomplete, you are entitled to request us to correct, amend or delete it
  * Portability: you may request that we send you any Personal Information that you have provided to us or ask that we send this information to a third party
  * Objection: you may object to us using your Personal Information where we use it based on our legitimate interests to do so
  * Restriction: you may request that we restrict the processing of your information where you believe it is inaccurate, our processing is unlawful, you believe we no longer need the information or if you have objected to our use of it
  * Automated Decision Making: where we undertake automated decision making (including profiling), which significantly affects you, you are entitled to object to such decision-making

#### Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, we do not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as Members. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any Personal Information to or on Theme Palace. In the event that we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [info[at]themepalace[dot]com](mailto:info@themepalace.com).

#### Links to Other Web Sites

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Service, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

#### Your Consent

By using this site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Changes To Our Privacy Policy

We may update its Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review this Policy periodically. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on this page, we will update the ‘last modified’ date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at [info[at]themepalace[dot]com](mailto:info@themepalace.com), or send mail to:  
Theme Palace, LLC  
2570 Bradford Sq NE  
Atlanta 30345
